RG 097, Connecticut Commission on the Arts
Connecticut State Library
- Series 4. Project Create, 1967-1970
  - Correspondence Report (Box 21)
    - Schedule - 2nd semester performances and consultant visits (Box 21)
    - Sandy and Caroline Paton tour (Box 21)
    - Feedback -second semi-program, 1969 (Box 21)
    - Prospective Consultants (Box 21)
    - Proposals, 2nd semester projections (Box 21)
    - Paperback Players, etc. (Box 21)
    - Paper bag project performance, etc. (Box 21)
    - Paper bag Player, Contract Agreement (Box 21)
  - Financial Records (Box 22)
    - Bernard Kates, Travel Expenses Form, 1967-1968 (Box 22)
    - Coordinators, Travel Expense Forms (Box 22)
    - Edna Kasle, Travel Expense Forms (Box 22)
    - Edward J.P. O’Connor, Expense Forms (Box 22)
    - Teacher’s Overtime, All Schools (Box 22)
    - Plimpton’s (Box 22)
    - Consultant Workshop, All Schools, September, January, February (Box 22)
    - Project Create, Hartford Office (Box 22)
    - Answering Service (Box 22)
    - 1968-69, 1968-1969 (Box 22)
    - Newsclip Service (Box 22)
    - Petty Cash (Box 22)
    - Postage (Box 22)
    - Rent (Box 22)
    - Salary Account (Box 22)
    - Workshop Weekend - Moodus (Box 22)
    - Telephone (Box 22)
    - Tom Spence - 16 mm animated film (Box 22)
    - Shirley Kaplan, slide presentation cost (Box 22)
    - Stationary, etc. (Box 22)
    - Producing Company (Box 22)
    - General Contracted Services (Box 22)
    - Photographics (Box 22)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 22)
    - Waterbury - B.W. Tinker School (Box 22)
    - Pomfret Community School (Box 22)
    - Hartford - Annie Fisher School (Box 22)
    - Groton, Eastern Point School (Box 22)
    - Bristol, Thomas H. Patterson School (Box 22)
    - New Haven - Baldwin School (Box 22)
    - Cornwall - Cornwall Consolidated School (Box 22)
    - Willimantic, F.R. Noble School (Box 22)
    - Bridgeport, Thomas Hooker School (Box 22)
    - Travel Expense Form (Box 22)
    - Travel Coordinators (Box 22)
    - Travel Consultants (Box 22)
    - Travel Create Staff (Box 22)
    - Bristol Consultants, Patterson School (Box 22)
    - Bridgeport Consultants, Hooker School (Box 22)
    - Cornwall Consultants, Cornwall Cons, School (Box 22)
    - Groton Consultants, Eastern Point School (Box 22)
    - Hartford Consultants, Baldwin School (Box 22)
    - New Haven Consultants, Baldwin School (Box 22)
    - Pomfret Consultants, Pomfret Com. School (Box 22)
    - Waterbury Consultants, B.W. Tinker School (Box 22)
    - Willimantic Consultants, F.R. Noble School (Box 22)
    - Requisition (Baldwin) (Box 22)
    - Requisition (Thomas Hooker) (Box 22)
    - Requisition (Cornwall) (Box 22)
    - Requisition (Pomfret) (Box 22)
    - Requisition (Annie Fisher) (Box 22)
    - Requisition (Willimantic) (Box 22)
    - Create Equipment Account, 1968-1969-1970 (Box 22)
    - 1969-70, 1969-1970 (Box 22)
    - Administrative Requisition, 1970 (Box 22)
    - Consultant Requisition, 1970 (Box 22)
    - Travel Requisition, 1970 (Box 22)
    - School Supplies, 1970 (Box 22)
    - Equipment (Box 22)
    - Video Equipment Schedule (Box 22)
    - Grace Nash (Box 22)
    - Studio 49, Hargail Music Press (Box 22)
    - Peripale - M. Hahner, Inc. (Box 22)
    - Budget (Box 22)
    - Budget Correspondence, Notes, etc. (Box 22)
    - Project Create Audit Report, 1969 June (Box 22)
    - Create Final Report, 1970 (Box 22)
    - Final Budget Report, 1967-1968 (Box 22)
    - Federal Budget Summary Forms and Worksheet (Box 22)
  - School Photographs, Slides, Snapshots, 1969-1970 (Box 58)
    - Airport Murals (Box 58)
    - Baldwin: New Haven (Box 58)
    - Thomas Hooker: Bridgeport (Box 58)
    - Groton (negatives) (Box 58)
    - Hobbit #2, Zulick, Noble School, Willimantic (Box 58)
    - Tom Spence (2 items) (Box 58)
    - Pomfret Community School (Box 58)
    - Willimantic Pictures - Noah’s Flood, Wendy Papakonstantis (Box 58)
    - Miscellaneous Negatives (Box 58)
    - Fisher (Box 58)
    - Annie Fisher, Hartford - Slides (Box 58)
    - Cornwall Consolidated School (Box 58)
    - Clive Thimpson Performance, Hill House (Box 58)
    - Noble School, Willimantic (Box 58)
- Series 5. Artists-in-Schools (A. I. S.) Program
  - School Files and Poetry Programs (Box 23)
    - J.F.K. High School, Waterbury, 1975-1976 (Box 23)
    - Crosby High School, Waterbury, 1975-1976 (Box 23)
    - Wallace Middle School, Waterbury, 1975-1976 (Box 23)
    - Wallace Middle School, Waterbury, 1974-1975 (Box 23)
    - J.F.K. High School. Waterbury, 1973-1974 (Box 23)
    - Webster School, Waterbury, 1972-1973 (Box 23)
    - Sprague School, Waterbury, 1971-1972 (Box 23)
    - Merriman School, Waterbury, 1973-1974 (Box 23)
  - (Box 23)
    - Mattatuck Community College, Waterbury (Box 23)
    - Waterbury Public Schools (Box 23)
    - Waterbury - Follow through early childhood education (Box 23)
    - Washington School, Waterbury (Box 23)
    - Maloney School, Waterbury (Box 23)
    - O’Neill - Southeast Connecticut, 1975-1976 (Box 23)
    - Quaker Hill, Waterford (Box 23)
    - O’Neill Project, 1974-1975 (Box 23)
    - O’Neill Project, 1973-1974 (Box 23)
    - Seaside (Retarded and Handicapped) Waterford (Box 23)
    - Waterford Country School (Box 23)
    - O’Neill Evaluation and Program Description (Box 23)
    - O’Neill Project, 1975-1976 (Box 23)
    - O’Neill Creative Arts in the Classroom Conference (Box 23)
    - Watertown Board of Education (Box 23)
    - Taft School (Box 23)
    - Conard High School (Box 23)
    - Day Treatment Service of C.R.E.C. (Box 23)
    - Renbrook School, West Hartford, 1976-1977 (Box 23)
    - Renbrook School, West Hartford, 1976-1977 (Box 23)
    - Talcott Jr. High School (Box 23)
    - Charter Oak School (Box 23)
    - Plant Junior High School (Box 23)
    - Northwest Catholic High School (Box 23)
    - St. Joseph College (Box 23)
    - Soloman Schacter Day School (Box 23)
    - West Hartford Public Schools (Box 23)
    - Hall High School (Box 23)
    - West Haven High School (Box 23)
    - West Haven Schools (Box 23)
    - West haven Neighborhood Music School (Box 23)
    - West Haven Forest School (Box 23)
    - Westport Art Council (Box 23)
    - Westport Youth Adult Council, Levitt Pavilion (Box 23)
    - Westport School Art Collection (Box 23)
    - Westport Public Schools (Box 23)
    - Westport Weston Arts Council, Seabury Center (Box 23)
    - Westport Alternative Jr. High School (Box 23)
    - Staples High School, Westport (Box 23)
    - Westport - Connecticut Center of Continuing Education (Box 23)
    - Westledge School (Box 23)
    - Wethersfield V.A.P. data document evaluation (Box 23)
    - Wethersfield, 1975-1976 (Box 23)
    - Wethersfield Fuller Elementary School (Box 23)
    - Wethersfield Public School, 1974-1975 (Box 23)
    - Wethersfield Mitchell School (Box 23)
    - Wethersfield High School (Box 23)
    - Willington Board of Education, 1976-1977 (Box 23)
    - Willimantic, William B. Sweeney (Box 23)
    - C.R.E.C. (Box 23)
    - Wilton Middle School (Box 23)
    - Windsor, J.F. Kennedy School (Box 23)
    - John Fitch School, Windsor (Box 23)
    - Windsor High School (Box 23)
    - Windsor Locks, 1974-1975 (Box 23)
    - Windsor Locks High School, V.A.P. (Box 23)
    - Windsor Locks High School, Student Writing (Box 23)
    - Windsor V.A.P. Sandra Moore, 1973-1974 (Box 23)
    - Windsor V.A.P. High School, Ed Oates (Box 23)
    - Windsor V.A.P. Sculpture, 1973 (Box 23)
    - Northwestern Regional School, Winsted (Box 23)
    - Northwest V.A.P., 1975-1976 (Box 23)
    - Northwestern Regional School, 1974-1975 (Box 23)
    - Amity Regional High School, District 5 (Box 23)
    - Beecher School South, Woodbridge (Box 23)
    - Nonnewuag High School, Woodbury (Box 23)
    - Mitchell School (Box 23)
    - Woodstock Public School, 1974-1975 (Box 23)
    - Woodstock Visting Artist Program (Box 23)
    - Woodstock Area Arts Council (Box 23)
    - Woodstock Public Schools (Box 23)
  - Poetry Program (Box 24)
    - Annhurst College (Box 24)
    - University of Bridgeport, Poetry Program (Box 24)
    - Central Connecticut State College (Box 24)
    - University of Connecticut (Box 24)
    - Eastern Connecticut State College (Box 24)
    - Fairfield University (Box 24)
    - Hotchkiss School (Box 24)
    - Manchester Community College (Box 24)
    - Quinnipiac College (Box 24)
    - Trinity College (Box 24)
    - Southern Connecticut State College (Box 24)
    - University of Hartford (Box 24)
    - Wesleyan University - “The Corner Store” –Performance Group (Box 24)
    - Western Connecticut State College (Box 24)
    - Berkshire School (Box 24)
    - Southbury School (Box 24)
    - Kent Summer Film Institute (Box 24)
    - Black Box (Publications) (Box 24)
    - Connecticut Association of Secondary Schools (Box 24)
    - Education Magazines (article) (Box 24)
    - Minneapolis Poetry Project (Box 24)
    - My Weekly Leader (Box 24)
    - Other Poet Organizations and Correspondence with them (Box 24)
    - Poetry Report from Kansas (Box 24)
    - Poets and Writers Newsletter C.O.D.A (Box 24)
    - Poets and Poetry Circuit Information (Box 24)
    - Poets Program, 1972-1973 (Box 24)
    - Poets Program, Prospective Poets, 1972-1973 (Box 24)
    - Poets Program, General Information (Box 24)
    - Poets Program, Grants History (Box 24)
    - Poetry Northwest, (Title III) (Box 24)
    - Poets Program - Planning for FY, 1973-1974 (Box 24)
    - Poets and Writers (Box 24)
    - Poets Program Prospective (Box 24)
    - Response from Poets, 1973-1974 (Box 24)
    - Responses from School, 1973-1974 (Box 24)
    - Stone Soup Poetry (Box 24)
    - Trinity Poetry Center (Box 24)
    - Writers - Resource lists (Box 24)
    - On Hiring a Poetry Evaluator (Box 24)
    - Morris L. Cogan (Box 24)
    - Colleges Evaluation of Poetry Programs (Box 24)
    - A.I.R. Business, 1973-1974 (Box 24)
    - Poets in the Colleges Program (Box 24)
    - Student Teacher Evaluation, Central Poets Program, 1972-1973 (Box 24)
    - Original Manuscript - Poets Report, 1972-1973 (Box 24)
    - Grants Application (Box 24)
    - Copies of the Poetry Book to … (Box 24)
    - Publishing Advice (Box 24)
    - Poetry Book, Publication Info (Box 24)
    - Poetry Book - Notes (Box 24)
    - Photos to be returned to: When book is completed (Box 24)
    - Drafts and ideas to be completed for poetry books (Box 24)
    - Southern Connecticut State College materials (Box 24)
    - Terry Stokes Correspondence Folder (Box 24)
  - Poetry Program and T.P.A.P. (Box 25)
    - Central Connecticut State College (Box 25)
    - General (Cogen - Administrator Proposals) (Box 25)
    - Northwest Connecticut Visiting Poets Program (Box 25)
    - Annhurst College (Box 25)
    - Eastern Connecticut State College (Box 25)
    - Visiting Artist Program (Box 25)
    - Education Programs Questionnaires, 1967-1974 (Box 25)
    - Education Division History Files, 1976 (Box 25)
    - ANISA - Comprehensive Arts Program - U. Mass/ Amherst (Box 25)
    - Evaluation Results - Tabulations (Box 25)
    - ECA assessment pt of Title VII plan (Box 25)
    - PWITS Questionnaire, 1975-1976 (Box 25)
    - Feedback from Past V.A.P.’s (Box 25)
    - T.P.A.P. applicants, 1976-1977 (Box 25)
    - T.P.A.P Fiscal and Narrative Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 25)
  - Schools Files (Box 26)
    - Rocky Hill - West Hill School (Box 26)
    - Roxbury - Booth Free School (Box 26)
    - Salisbury - Board of Education (Box 26)
    - Salisbury School (Box 26)
    - Saybrook Alternative School (Box 26)
    - Valley Arts Council (Box 26)
    - Daytop, Inc. - Shelton (Box 26)
    - Shelton - Booth Hill, 1975-1976 (Box 26)
    - Shelton - Booth Hill School, 1974-1975 (Box 26)
    - Shelton - Huntington School, 1975-1976 (Box 26)
    - Shelton - Huntington School, 1974-1975 (Box 26)
    - Shelton - Sunnyside School (Box 26)
    - Simsbury - Tootin School, 1976-1977 (Box 26)
    - Shelton - Elizabeth Shelton School (Box 26)
    - Simsbury - Latimer Lane School (Box 26)
    - Simsbury - High School (Box 26)
    - Simsbury - Public Schools (Box 26)
    - Simsbury - Ethel Walker School (Box 26)
    - Simsbury - McLean Home (Box 26)
    - Somers - Somers Poetry Program (Box 26)
    - Somers - Somers Correctional School (Box 26)
    - Southbury - Juvenile Justice Collaboration (Box 26)
    - Southington - Board of Education (Box 26)
    - Southington - A.I.S. Video, 1975-1976 (Box 26)
    - Southington - Hatton Elementary School, 1975-1976 (Box 26)
    - Southington - Board of Education, 1974-1975 (Box 26)
    - Southington - Documentation of Video Residency, 1975-1976 (Box 26)
    - Southington - Milldale Elementary School, 1974-1975 (Box 26)
    - Southington - V.A.P. Evaluation, 1974-1975 (Box 26)
    - Southington - Kennedy Jr. High School (Box 26)
    - Southington - High School, 1973-1974 (Box 26)
    - Southington - De Paolo Jr. High School, 1973-1974 (Box 26)
    - Southington - Workshops, 1973-1974 (Box 26)
    - Southington - V.A.P. Secondary Level, 1972-1973 (Box 26)
    - Southington - From Pancake to Pantomine to Progress (Box 26)
    - South Windsor - Cultural Arts (Box 26)
    - Sprague School (Box 26)
    - Stafford School System (Box 26)
    - Stafford High School (Box 26)
    - Ashford Elementary School (Box 26)
    - Stratford Lordship School (Box 26)
    - Stratford High School (Box 26)
    - Storrs - UConn Women’s Center (Box 26)
    - Storrs - UConn Center for Open Education (Box 26)
    - Suffield - High School (Box 26)
    - Suffield -Visiting Artists Day, 1975 (Box 26)
    - Suffield - Academy (Box 26)
    - Suffield - Public Schools (Box 26)
    - Terryville High School (Box 26)
    - Thomaston - Grove Street School, 1976-1977 (Box 26)
    - Tolland - Hicks Memorial School, 1976-1977 (Box 26)
    - Torrington - High School (Box 26)
    - Trumbull High School (Box 26)
    - Union Elementary School (Box 26)
    - Unionville - West District School (Box 26)
    - Wallingford - Mark T. Sheehan High School (Box 26)
    - Washington - Shepaug Valley Middle School (Box 26)
    - Washington - Wyckham- Gunnery (Box 26)
    - Washington - Consolidated (Box 26)
    - Washington - Middle School Evaluation and Student Work, 1972 (Box 26)
    - Waterbury - Board of Education Art Coordination (Box 26)
    - Waterbury - John F. Kennedy High School, 1974-1975 (Box 26)
    - Enfield School Arts Coordinator (Box 27)
    - Enrico Fermi High School - Enfield (Box 27)
    - Enfield Music Department (Box 27)
    - Fairfield Public Schools (Box 27)
    - Fairfield Andrew Warde High School (Box 27)
    - Fairfield Timothy Dwight (Box 27)
    - Falls Village - Housatonic Valley Regional High School (Box 27)
    - Farmington Public Schools (Box 27)
    - Farmington West District Elementary School (Box 27)
    - Glastonbury - Buttonball Lane School (Box 27)
    - Glastonbury High School (Box 27)
    - Glastonbury High School (Box 27)
    - Glastonbury Public Schools (Box 27)
    - Glastonbury Hebron Avenue School (Box 27)
    - Glastonbury Naubuc School (Box 27)
    - Greenwich - A.I.S. film, 1975-1976 (Box 27)
    - Greenwich - North Street School (Box 27)
    - Greenwich - Public Schools - A.I.S. film, 1975-1976 (Box 27)
    - Greenwich - Public Schools, 1974-1975 (Box 27)
    - Greenwich - Whitby School (Box 27)
    - Greenwich - Whitby School, 1975-1976 (Box 27)
    - Greenwich - Whitby School, 1974-1975 (Box 27)
    - Greenwich - C.D. (Box 27)
    - Greenwich - Parkway School (Box 27)
    - Greenwich - Western Jr. High School (Box 27)
    - Groton - Whames Valley Community Council (Box 27)
    - Groton - Seeley Elementary School (Box 27)
    - Guilford Public Schools (Box 27)
    - Hamden - High School, 1976-1977 (Box 27)
    - Hamden - West Woods Elementary Schools (Box 27)
    - Hamden - Spring Glen School (Box 27)
    - Hamden - High School (Box 27)
    - Hampton - Consolidated School (Box 27)
    - Hartford - P.R.A.X.I.S. Experimental (Box 27)
    - Hartford - Creative Arts Community (Box 27)
    - Hartford - Neighborhood Center (Box 27)
    - Hartford - Correctional School District, 1976-1977 (Box 27)
    - Hartford - Arts High School - Capitol Region (Box 27)
    - Hartford - Department of Corrections - Schools (Box 27)
    - Hartford - Correctional Schools District, 1975-1976 (Box 27)
    - Hartford - Public Schools, 1975-1976 (Box 27)
    - Greater Hartford Arts Council, 1975-1976 (Box 27)
    - Hartford - Arts Council - Education Committee (Box 27)
    - Hartford - Greater Hartford Community College (Box 27)
    - Hartford - Board of Education (Box 27)
    - Hartford - Clarence A. Barbour School (Box 27)
    - Hartford - Blue Hills Civic Association (Box 27)
    - Hartford - Clark Elementary School (Box 27)
    - Hartford - Fox Middle School (Box 27)
    - Hartford - Commission on Higher Education (Box 27)
    - Hartford - Annie Fisher School (Box 27)
    - Hartford - Hartford High School (Box 27)
    - Hartford - S.A.N.D. (Box 28)
    - Hartford - Bulkeley High School (Box 28)
    - Hartford - Naylor School (Box 28)
    - Hartford -Mark Twain School (Box 28)
    - Hartford -Twin Valley Upward Bound (Trinity College) (Box 28)
    - Hartford - Barnard Brown School (Box 28)
    - Hartford - Kennelly School (Box 28)
    - Hartford - McCook Hospital - University of Connecticut (Box 28)
    - Hartford - Waverly School (Box 28)
    - Hartford - Weaver evaluation (Box 28)
    - Hartford - Weaver High School (Box 28)
    - Hartford - Noah Webster School (Box 28)
    - Hartford - Quirk Middle School (Box 28)
    - Hartford - S.A.N.D. everywhere school (Box 28)
    - Hartford - West Middle School (Box 28)
    - Hartford - Shanti School (Box 28)
    - Hartford - Artists-in-Schools Workshop, 1974 February (Box 28)
    - Hartford - YMCA, Hartford Region (Box 28)
    - Hartford - Wilkinson School (Box 28)
    - Hartford - Ballet School Project (Box 28)
    - Hebron Elementary School (Box 28)
    - Haddam Junior High School (Regional School District #17) (Box 28)
    - Killingworth Elementary School (Box 28)
    - Lakeville - Hotchkiss School (Box 28)
    - Lebanon Public Schools (Box 28)
    - Ledyard Parks and Recreation (Box 28)
    - Ledyard Public Schools (Box 28)
    - Litchfield School (Box 28)
    - Litchfield Womogo Regional High School (Box 28)
    - Litchfield Dance, 1975-1976 (Box 28)
    - Litchfield Dance residency, 1974-1975 (Box 28)
    - Madison, 1975-1976 (Box 28)
    - Madison - Country School (Box 28)
    - Madison - Schools, 1974-1975 (Box 28)
    - Madison, 1972-1974 (Box 28)
    - Madison - Project Stage (Box 28)
    - Madison - Hand High School (Box 28)
    - Madison - Project Learn, 1972 (Box 28)
    - Manchester - Bennett Jr. High School (Box 28)
    - Manchester - Bower School (Box 28)
    - Manchester - Children’s School (Box 28)
    - Manchester - Three Guys (Box 28)
    - Manchester - School Community (Box 28)
    - Manchester - High School (Box 28)
    - Manchester - East Catholic High School (Box 28)
    - Manchester - Bulkeley School (Box 28)
    - Mansfield - Longley School (Box 28)
    - Marlborough - Arts Council V.A.P. (Box 28)
    - Marlborough - Elementary School (Box 28)
    - Meriden - Pulaski Elementary School, 1975-1976 (Box 28)
    - Meriden, 1975-1976 (Box 28)
    - Meriden - Pulaski School (Box 28)
    - Meriden - Barry School (Box 28)
    - Middlebury-Southbury - Pomeroug School District #15 (Box 29)
    - Middlebury - Westoner School (Box 29)
    - Middlefield - Memorial Middle School Regional School District #15 (Box 29)
    - Middlefield - Center School and Chestnut Hill School, 1972-1973 (Box 29)
    - Middlefield - Durham-Chestnut Hill and center School, V.A.P. (Box 29)
    - Middlefield - Durham V.A.P., 1973-1974 (Box 29)
    - Middlefield - Independent Day School (Box 29)
    - Middletown - Center for Creative Youth - Special Arts High School, Summer of 1977 (Box 29)
    - Middletown - Wesleyan University World Music Program, 1975-1976 (Box 29)
    - Middletown - Public Schools, 1976-1977 (Box 29)
    - Middletown - Arts Council (Box 29)
    - Middletown - World Music Program, 1974-1975-1976 (Box 29)
    - Middletown - Wesleyan Music Program, Cont., 1972-1974 (Box 29)
    - Middletown - Wesleyan Music Program, Cont., 1972-1974 (Box 29)
    - Middletown - Music Report, 1973 November (Box 29)
    - Middletown - Woodrow Wilson High School (Box 29)
    - Middletown - High School, School within a school (Box 29)
    - Middletown - Lawrence School (Box 29)
    - Middletown - High School (Box 29)
    - Middletown - Area Cooperative Alternative School, Inc. (Box 29)
    - Hartford - Center for Creative Youth (Box 29)
    - Milford - Milford Academy, A.I.S. visiting artist application, 1976-1977 (Box 29)
    - Milford - Public Schools (Box 29)
    - Monroe Public Schools, V.A.P., 1974-1975 (Box 29)
    - Evaluation - V.A.P., 1976-1975 (Box 29)
    - Monroe - Public Schools, Art Specialist (Box 29)
    - Montville - Montville High School (Box 29)
    - Montville - Summer Theatre Program, 1976-1977 (Box 29)
    - Naugatuck - Naugatuck youth Services (Box 29)
    - Naugatuck - Schools, Special Services (Box 29)
    - New Britain - Board of Education (Box 29)
    - New Britain - Elihu Burritt School (Box 29)
    - New Canaan - Center School (Box 29)
    - New Hartford - Antolini Middle School (Box 29)
    - New Hartford - Elementary School (Box 29)
    - Barkhamsted Elementary School (Box 29)
    - New Haven - Educational Center for the Arts, 1976-1977 (Box 29)
    - New Haven - A.C.E.S., 1976-1977 (Box 29)
    - New Haven - A.C.E.S., 1976-1977 (Box 29)
    - New Haven - Educational Center for the Arts (Box 29)
    - New Haven - Project Search (A.C.E.S.) (Box 29)
    - New Haven - Schools, 1975-1976 (Box 29)
    - New Haven - Title Ten C.E.T.A. Educational Prog. (Box 29)
    - New Haven - Edgewood School (Box 29)
  - A.I.S. by Art Form (Box 30)
    - Poetry and Writing (Box 30)
      - Floyce Alexander (Box 30)
      - Allan Appel (Box 30)
      - Adele Aldridge (Box 30)
      - Helman Asarnow (Box 30)
      - Frank Asch (Box 30)
      - Ron Atkinson (Box 30)
      - Richie Baker (Box 30)
      - Tom Barnes (Box 30)
      - Michael Benedikt (Box 30)
      - Carol Berge (Box 30)
      - Barry Brissman (Box 30)
      - Poetryk Denise M. Cassens (Box 30)
      - Kasrof Chantikian (Box 30)
      - Kasrof Chantikian (Box 30)
      - James V. Cervantes - Writer - NR (Box 30)
      - James Coleman (Box 30)
      - Paul Corrigan - Writer, playwright, director (Box 30)
      - Ruth Daigon (Box 30)
      - Dick Davis (Box 30)
      - William Doreski - Poetry (Box 30)
      - Richard B. Fried - Poetry (Box 30)
      - Brendan Galvin (Box 30)
      - Galen Green (Box 30)
      - Walter Griffin, Poet (Box 30)
      - Valerie Harms (Box 30)
      - William Joyce (Box 30)
      - Ann Kelleher (Box 30)
      - Thomas Lanter, Playwright (Box 30)
      - Crispin Larangeira (Box 30)
      - Todd S. J. Lawson (Box 30)
      - William Logan, Poetry (Box 30)
      - Lanie London, Playwright (Box 30)
      - Phillip Lopate (Box 30)
      - Everette Maddox, Poetry (Box 30)
      - Jack Matthews, Poetry (Box 30)
      - David McCain (Box 30)
      - Irma McClaurin (Box 30)
      - Susan Miller (Box 30)
      - Larry Maffi (Box 30)
      - Rebecca Newth, Poetry (Box 30)
      - Charles Plymell (Box 30)
      - Bob Pollack, Journalism (Box 30)
      - Brooks Von Ranson (Box 30)
      - Larry Rappaport, Poetry (Box 30)
      - Roshelle Ratner (Box 30)
      - Joseph Regan (Box 30)
      - Michael Rowe (Box 30)
      - Lennard Royal (Box 30)
      - Raphail Rudnik (Box 30)
      - Chester Schnepf (Box 30)
      - Hugh Seidman (Box 30)
      - Warren Slesinger (Box 30)
      - G.P. Skratz (Box 30)
      - Kirtland Alan Snyder (Box 30)
      - Rita Stainton (Box 30)
      - Stephen Stavros (Box 30)
      - Craig Sterry (Box 30)
      - Jody Swilky (Box 30)
      - Tobe (Box 30)